<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index of ~ on RadioGeek</title>
    <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index of ~ on RadioGeek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Root; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://radiogeek.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Communications with the crew</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/mir/voice-comms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/mir/voice-comms/</guid>
      <description>My first radio contact with MIR Orbital Station My first radio contact with the late MIR Orbital Station (MIR in Russian means PEACE) dates back to 1996. At that time, Russian cosmonaut Valery Korzun was the commander of the mission and an assiduous presence on the radio frequencies. Unfortunately, and for logistical reasons, I could not make a recording of the QSO. It was my first contact with a manned space mission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEXUS Fuji-Oscar 99</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/nexus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/nexus/</guid>
      <description>Here’s my recording of CW Beacon - drifted
Frequency 437.073 MHz
Mode CW 20
Timeframe:
2020-07-31 20:53:29
2020-07-31 21:00:36
Fuji-Oscar 99
Frequencies:
• 437.075 MHz CW Telemetry
• 435.900 MHz FSK AX.25 / π/4 shift QPSK CCSDS
• SSB/CW transponder
– 145.900-145.930 MHz Uplink
– 435.880-435.910 MHz Downlink
NEXUS Blog http://tinyurl.com/NEXUS-Sat-Blog
JAMSAT in Google English http://tinyurl.com/JAMSAT
IARU Frequency Coordination http://www.amsatuk.me.uk/iaru/finished_detail.php?serialnum=535
Your browser does not support the audio element.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DA0SPUTNIK</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/da0sputnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 16:39:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/da0sputnik/</guid>
      <description>On October 4th 2007 at 00:00 MESZ a balloon was launched from a team of radio amateurs at the Sternwarte Bochum/Germany. This is of course not really a satellite. It carried a beacon with the callsign DA0SPUTNIK which was transmitting information and audio recordings of the first artificial satellite Sputnik-1 which had been launched 50 years before.
Your browser does not support the audio element.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RAFT Amateur Radio Satellite Project</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/raft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/raft/</guid>
      <description>RAFT de-orbited on 30 May 2007 after 5 months in space. Here’s an excerpt from Raft’s webpage:
BYE-BYE RAFT: Last packet captured was by PE1ITR at 01:45:10. . Nothing heard on the next USA pass at about 0300z on 30 May 2007. Total mission time for RAFT since the 21 December Launch was about 5 months and 9 days. . During the last 24 hours, the RAFT temperature rose by 30 deg C in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Communications with the crew</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/iss/voice-comms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 16:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/iss/voice-comms/</guid>
      <description>My 1st radio contact with the International Space Station Susan Helms was a resident of the International Space Station (ISS) as flight engineer for over five months in 2001. While participating in ISS Expedition 2, she was a very active astronaut in the field of hamradio communications. It was also during Expedition 2 that the amateur radio equipment was installed, allowing us hams to contact the astronauts. You can hear my first conversation with her (recorded on 23rd June 2001).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts with students</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/iss/contacts-with-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/iss/contacts-with-students/</guid>
      <description>Students in Rio de Janeiro talk to the Space Station A multi-point telebridge took place today between students of the American School of Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, and astronaut Chris Cassidy KF5KDR, using OR4ISS callsign, aboard the International Space Station.
Chris Cassidy
SOURCE: NASA
A multi-point telebridge contact means that each student will be on the telebridge from their own home: the students will be talking with the ISS from their homes over phone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AISTECHSAT-3</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/aistechsat-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/satellites/aistechsat-3/</guid>
      <description>Reception of FSK AX.100 Mode 5 9600 from AISTECHSAT-3 Satellite.
Based on the CubeSat-2U platform, AISTECHSAT-3 was developed by GOMSpace and Aistech. The satellites in this series provide aircraft tracking via an ADS-B receiver. There is also a two-way communication system for sending and receiving automatic information from vessels or remote assets around the world.
Receção @SatNOGS do AISTECHSAT-3, satélite desenvolvido pela @GomSpaceGroup GOMSpace e pela @AistechSpace.https://t.co/eDI36rY3el pic.twitter.com/DqQO3OfyeS
&amp;mdash; Paulo Pinto CT1ETE (@CT1ETE) August 1, 2020  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi!
My name is Paulo Pinto and my ham callsign is CT1ETE.
I have been passionate about communications since I was 13 years old. I obtained my amateur radio license in 1993 and since then I have been dedicating a large part of my free time to DX, Satellites and SWL.
I am lover of CW (Morse code) and I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to improve the speed of my decoding ability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Root</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/root/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:47:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/root/</guid>
      <description>you need to be root to access this folder. try with sudo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/paulopinto/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://radiogeek.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://radiogeek.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>RadioGeek is a collaborative website with radio related content.
It is a website open to all those who want to share knowledge, information and documentation related to radiocommunications, with a special focus on satellite communications and manned space missions.
The website structure is simple, based on a folder system, in which each project participant will have a folder with their name. Within each folder each participant can place content for sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>